A Guide to the Gravely Family Papers, 1753-1988
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Personal files, Richard P. Gravely, Jr.
  - Education articles (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Enlargers, Dark Room, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Erwin, John Thomas (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Family, Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Fernald, Alberta Gravely (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Fernald, Benjamin G., 1897-1978 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Films, prints, processing (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Forest Products Research Society (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Franklin Co. Records, 1939-1986 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Genealogy article (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - William Goebel poster (Kentucky governor) (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Grandfather clocks (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Gravely, Benjamin F., 1818-1882 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Gravely, Benjamin F., Jr. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Gravely, Ernest (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Gravely, Fenton (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Gravely, Frank T. (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Gravely, Harold (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Gravely, Harry C., Jr. (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Gravely, Henry Clay (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Gravely, Henry Clay, Writing analysis (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Gravely, Henry Clay, House (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Gravely, Henry Clay, House Inventory, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Gravely, J.O.W. (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Gravely, John Thomas, 1849-1893 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Gravely, Joseph, estate, 1835 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Gravely, Julia C. (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Gravely, Nancy Watkins (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Gravely, Paul (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Gravely, Peyton Anderson (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Gravely, Peyton B. (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Gravely, Reginald Whitten (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Gravely, Richard P., Sr. (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Gravely, Richard P., Sr. (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Gravely, Richard P., Sr., Heirs (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Gravely, Richard P., Jr., correspondence, 1914-1984 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Gravely, Richard P., Jr., University of Virginia grades, 1931-1933 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Gravely, Richard P., Jr., clippings, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Gravely, Richard P., Jr., art and maps (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Gravely, Richard P., III, 1937 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Gravely, Richard P., III, 1938-1949 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Gravely, Richard P., III, ball cap (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Gravely, Richard P., III, polio clippings, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Gravely, Richard P., III, hotel bills for parents while in hospital, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Gravely, Richard P., III, letters concerning illness, 28 August-6 September 1949 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Gravely, Richard P., III, sympathy notes (flowers), September 1949 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Gravely, Richard P., III, sympathy telegrams, September 1949 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Gravely, Richard P., III, sympathy cards and notes, 5-6 September 1949 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Gravely, Richard P., III, sympathy cards and notes, 7-8 September 1949 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Gravely, Richard P., III, sympathy cards and notes, 9 September 1949 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Gravely, Richard P., III, sympathy cards and notes, 10-14 and 18 September 1949 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Gravely, Richard P., III, sympathy cards and notes, 20-21 September 1949 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Gravely, Richard P., III, sympathy cards and notes, October 1949 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Gravely, Richard P., III, sympathy cards and notes, no date, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Gravely, Richard P., III, contributions to Polio Foundation, Henry County chapter, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Gravely, Richard P., III, miscellaneous (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Gravely, Robert M. (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Gravely, Samuel (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Gravely, Thomas Eleanor (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Gravely family (Richard P. Gravely, Jr.) (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Gravely family wedding clippings (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Gravely family obituary clippings (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Gravely family miscellaneous clippings (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Gravely family (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Gravely family, Misc. History (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Gravely family, Misc. history (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Gravely family, Misc. history (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Gravely family, Blacks (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - The Amazing Storey of the Gravelys in America (Box 31)
  - Gravely town, Hertford County (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Gravely & Miller (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Gravely Furniture Co., Inc. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Gravely Furniture Co., Inc. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Gravely Furniture Co., Inc., annual reports 1942-1985 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Gravely Furniture Co., Stock (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Gravely Furniture Co., Pulaksi (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Gravely Novelty Furniture, 1926-1975 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Gravely Tractors (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Great Wagon Road Pres. Comm., 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Hampson, Sadie Gravely (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Helms, Virginia Gravely (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Henry County Bicentennial Commission (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Henry County elections (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Henry County Plywood Corp., 1948-1985 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Historical (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Image of a Scholar, RPG, Sr. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Insurance (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Insurance claim, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Insurance claim, Gravely, Bennie M., 1977 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Integral Shaped Edge licenses (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Joe W. Gravely Co. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Lamineer Patent (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Land: Clark, J. Gravely tracts (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Leatherwood store (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Lee, Hope Gravely (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Legislation (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Maps (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Martinsville- H.C. Women's Club (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Memoranda, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - MENSA (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Microfilm work (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Military service, 1942-1946 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Henry G. Mullens check, 13 December 1895 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Mullins land; Old Iron Works Road (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Mullins, Samuel J., Estate (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - New Orleans postcards (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Obituary clippings (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Parks (Martinsville) (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Patent, formed cords, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Payments, 1938-1952 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Photography, General (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Photography, Old Cameras, etc. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Pittsylvania Co. Service Authority, 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Religion--clippings and tracts (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Remodeling, 1916 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Reprints, xerography (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Ridgeway clocks origin (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Rosebud Missionary Society, 1919 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Science clippings (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Science Correspondence Club, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Scott, Ella Penn, Letters, 1867-1871 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Southern Henry Co. Hydro Dam (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Swivel Unit patent (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Telephone directories (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Thomas, C.Y., Estate (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Thomas, Susan R. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Thomas Manufacturing Co. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Tobacco advertisement stencils (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Trusteeship (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - University of Virginia (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Virginia CSA Presidential ticket, 1861 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Magazine of History and Biography, January 1974 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Museum of Natural History, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Virginia State Library and Archives, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Wood technology (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous--numbers and math (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Series III: Personal files, Philately, Richard P. Gravely, Jr.
  - AMG, 1955-1959 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - AMG Catalogue pages (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Bush, Joseph V., 1953-1959 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Everett, Morris, 1975-1979 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Flowers, G.W. Collection, Duke University, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Geijsbeek, William R., 1975 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Hendershott, Gary, 1980-1981 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Holden, Horace, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Holden family, Purchases from, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Holden material, 1962-1963 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Kaufmann, John W., 1981 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Henry Co. C.Y. Thomas letters (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Wineburgh Philatelic Res. Lib., 1980 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous individuals, 1963-1978 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Inventory, RPG stamp auctions, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Inventory, RPG stamp sale no. 1, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Catalogue, Ivy, Dalton sales, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Ivy, Gravely, Anderson Sales, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Ivy, Empire sale, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Ivy, Steve, RPG Confederate sale, 1963-1982 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Ivy, Steve, Philatelic auctions, 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Ivy, Steve, Contract, 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Ivy, Steve, RPG philatelic sale, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Stephens, A.H. Confederate covers (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Stephens, A.H. Papers (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Stephens, A.H., Letters (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Stephens, A.H., Letters about, 1956-1971 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Stephens, A.H., Misc. letters about, 1961-1965 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Stephens, A.H. Exhibition, 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Stephens, A.H., Misc., 1962-1964 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Stephens, A.H., NY cancellation, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Stephens, A.H., Copies, 1963-1975 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Confederate stamp alliance, 1944-1961 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Sale catalogues (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Sale of stamps (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Price lists, Confederate, 1895-1907 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Stamp catalogues, 1947-1950 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Sale of collections, 1980-1982 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Cancellation, testing, 1976-1978 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Envelope World, 1949-1952 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Postal Stationary (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Ft. Warren POW Covers (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Glen stamps (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Blue Ridge Airport Dedication, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Augusta (Ga.) CSA hand stamped (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Sacramento (Ca.), 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Ten-cent frame line of CSA (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Stamped envelopes watermark, 1975-1976 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Augusta (Ga.) Hand stamped, 1968-1969 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Confederate paid 4, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous clippings (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Stamp newspaper clippings (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Stamp newspaper clippings (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Stamp newspaper clippings (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Series IV: Genealogical notes
  - Anglin-Athey families (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Clark, Harold Gravely (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Dyer family (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Gravely, Edmund (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Gravely, Francis (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Gravely, George (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Gravely, Jabez (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Gravely, James (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Gravely, John (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Gravely, Joseph (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Gravely, Joseph (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Gravely, Joseph (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Gravely, Joseph H.H. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Gravely, Joseph Jackson (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Gravely, Lewis (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Gravely, Mary (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Gravely, Peyton (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Gravely, Willis (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Gravely family (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Gravely family (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Gravely family, Henry County (Va.) (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Gravely family, Henry County (Va.), Tax (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Gravely family, Land surveys (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Gravely family, Tax lists (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Gravely, Thomas, Watkins family, Halifax and Pittsylania Counties (Va.) (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Hamlett family (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Lyne, Wickliffe C. (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Martin family (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Martin family, Bible and autograph (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - McCabe family (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Mullins, David (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Mullins, Henry Green (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Mullins, Samuel J. (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Mullins family (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Mullins family (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Mullins-Hill-Parks families (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Payne-Gravely families (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Reamey family (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Smith family (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Starling family (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Thomas, C.Y. (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Thomas, C.Y. (Kit) (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Thomas, Frank Watkins (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Thomas, George (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Thomas John Watkins (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Thomas, Patrick (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Thomas, Phillip (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Thomas, William (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Thomas family (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Thomas family (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Thomas family (C.Y. Thomas) (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Thomas family (Caswell County, NC) (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Thomas family (Halifax County, Va.) (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Thomas family (Henry County, Va.) (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Thomas family (Pittsylvania County, Va.) (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Thomas-Watkins families (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Watkins family (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Gravely, Richard P., Pedigree (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Series V: Subject files
  - Accessories (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Account books, 1879-1904 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Agriculture (Bowen & Mercer; J. P. Warrenfeltz Company; J. Van Lindley Nursery Company) (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Department of Agriculture (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Almanack (horse, livestock and slave data), 1805 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - American Money, 9 September 1896 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Armenian and Syrian Child Relief (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Armour and Company (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Austin-Western Company, Ltd. (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Automobile Touring Club of America (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - B. A. Gravely & Company--Leatherwood Store (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - B. F. Gravely & Sons (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - B. F. Gravely & Sons brand formulas (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - B. F. Gravely & Sons labels (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - B. F. Gravely & Sons papers (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - B. F. Gravely & Sons stationary (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - B.F. Gravely & Sons vs. B.F. Gravely & Sons, 1888 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - B. F. Gravely & Sons trademark--My Maryland Superior Pounds, 14 June 1881 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - B. F. & R. P. Gravely Company (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - B. F. & R. P. Gravely Company wood insulation material (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - B. J. Gravely & Company (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Babson's Statistical Organization Weekly Barometer and Composite Plot,1912 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Babson's Statistical Organization Weekly Barometer and Composite Plot,1913 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Babson's Statistical Organization June and July Publications Received,1918 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Benj. F. Gravely Oriental Languages (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Blacksmith's account book, 1824-1825 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Book keeping (Berry Benson) (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Botanical/biological interests (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Boxes, storage and file (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Boyd's City Dispatch (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Bradstreet Company, 1902-1904 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Buckingham's Dye for the Whiskers (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Buffalo Specialty Manufacturing Company (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Building specifications (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - C.S. Garrett and Son (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Canal boat woodcuts (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Certificates, commissions, discharges (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Charlotte Electric Railway (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Chattanooga Medicine Company (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Check stubs (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Church plans (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Clark, Ainslie & and Company (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Clippings (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Clothes and linen (Burton's; The Linen Mart; Stein-Bloch Styles) (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Colleges (Eastman's Business College; Massey Business College; Roanoke College) (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Computers (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Confederate currency (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - County Clerks, Henry County (Va.) (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Court records, Henry County (Va.) (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Court records, Henry County (Va.) (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Currency, including Confederate and local (Civil War) (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - D.H. Spencer & Sons, Inc. (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - D. H. Spencer & Sons, Inc.--prices and tobacco pouch ads (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Dan River Power and Manufacturing (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Danville and Western Railway Company (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution applications, William S. Battle ancestor (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution Dedications (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Day book, J.T. Gravely, 1856 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Diary, Gravely, Ann Hope Thomas, 1881-1883 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Diary, Thomas, Susy, 1879-1882 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Drawings (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - East River Mill (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Edward E. Epps and Company (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Election materials, 1853-1912 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Ephemera (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Equipment and building supplies (Air Tight Steel Tank Company; Akron Tire Company, Inc.; American Steel and Wire Company; Fenton Metallic Manufacturing Company; Wheeling Corrugating Company) (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - F. E. Patrick Company, 1893 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - F. E. Patrick Company, 1894 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - F. E. Patrick Company, 1895-1896 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - F. E. Patrick Company, 1902 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Fernald, William (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - First National Bank, Danville (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - First National Bank, Martinsville (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Flat Top National Bank (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Floor, carpet, and products (Johnson's Wax; McDowell & Company, Inc.) (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Food (Consumers Fish Company; Delane Brown; Frank E. Davis Fish Company; Frostee; Mt. Olive Pickle Company) (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Georgia-Carolina Power Company (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Glover's Imperial Dog Remedy (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Gravely, Richard P., Library board appointment, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Gravely Furniture Company (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Gravely Novelty Furniture Company (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Gravely Novelty Furniture Company (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - H. A. Ford Company (auction and sale) (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Haight & Freese (banking house) (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Hammer plates (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Hatcher Scales Company (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - The Hayner Distillery (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Henry County Plywood Corporation (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Herald Publishing Co. 1882-1887 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Howser, James R., 1864-1865 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - I. C. Hirsch-Iron-Steel & Rail Company (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Importers and Traders National Bank (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Instructional manuals (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Insurance (American Casualty Company; Hanover Fire Insurance Company of New York; Insurance Company of New York; Northwest Mutual Life Insurance Company) (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Insurance policies, Gravely, H.C., 1903-1927 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Insurance policies, 1878-1981 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Internal Revenue Service (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Irish Road (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Ironman Fire Control System (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - J. L. Hopkins & Company (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - J. P. Pleasants & Sons (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - James Fugle & Company (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Jayne's Medical Almanac, 1849, containing ads for B. A. Gravely & Company's Leatherwood Store (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - King Mantel Company (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Kiplinger Washington Letter, 17 May 1930 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Leatherwood Land Company, 1979-1984 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Lee, Hope Gravely, 1910 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Letterhead samples (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Literary (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Manchester Paint and Oil Company (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Martinsville telephone directory (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Maryland and Pennsylvania Railroad (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Mathematics book, Gravely, Luci E. (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Dr. Otto Mayer (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Medicines, Ointments, etc. (Conrad's Tubes; Daniel's Electro-Magnetic Liniment; Dr. Shoop Family Medicine Company; Portsmouth Lavender Salts; Success Nasal Syringe) (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Memo and address book, Gravely, H.C. (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Microfilm materials, Virginia State Library and Archives (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Milton, NC (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Montgomery Ward & Company (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Moody's Investors Services, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Moravian diaries 1753 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Music (The Etude; RCA Radiola 28; Regina Music Box Company; Walter D. Moses and Company) (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Mutual Building & Loan Association, Martinsville (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - N. H. Turbeville & Company (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - N. W. Harris & Company (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - National Exchange Bank of Roanoke (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - New Process Company (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - New York Price Current (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Old Dominion Matrimonial Association (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - One Man in Two Worlds, Henry County (Va.) History, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - H. A. Orrick Baltimore Stock Exchange Sales,1902 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - H. A. Orrick Baltimore Stock Exchange Sales,1903 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - H. A. Orrick Baltimore Stock Exchange Sales,1904 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - H. A. Orrick Baltimore Stock Exchange Sales,1905 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - H. A. Orrick Baltimore Stock Exchange Sales,1912 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - H. A. Orrick Baltimore Stock Exchange Sales,1913 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - H. A. Orrick Baltimore Stock Exchange Sales,1914 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - P & G. Gravely, Tobacco book, 1823-1836 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Paint, gold (Paul Oppermann) (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Paper products (American Writing Paper Company; Clark Paper and Manufacturing Company; Marcus Ward's Pronger Bond; sample) (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Photography (Burke and Jones; Eastman Kodak; Photo-Beacon; Tennant and Ward) (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Piedmont Trust Bank, Martinsville (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Post Office (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Post Office department matters, 1871-1914 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Publications--books (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Publications--magazines and journals (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Publications--subscription services (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Pullman Company (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Purcell, Ladd & Company (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Raymond & Whitcomb Company/Fifth Third Union Trust Company (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Recipe books (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Report cards (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Richmond (Va.), The Tobacco Centre (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Richmond and Danville Railroad Company (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Riverside and Dan River Cotton Mills (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Sears, Roebuck and Company (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Shenandoah National Park Association (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Slave birth records (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Slaydon family (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Southern Pacific Railroad Company (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Southern Stamp and Stationary Company (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Statements, President's reports (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - T. F. Park & Company (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Tax forms, 1839-1917 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Tax forms, Gravely, Jabez and Benjamin, 1864-1865 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Telephone equipment (Ericsson Telephone Company; Kellogg Swithcboard and Supply Company) (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Time magazine, 24 November 1952 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Tobacco cards, wrappers (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Tobacco labels--B. F. Gravely's Best Pounds, P. B. Gravely Tobacco Company (Danville) (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Tobacco seed packets (Box 45, Folder 17)